本字幕由「泉水渗透进字幕组」制作
■
翻译&时轴: yojoU      听写: Whisper      压制: FFmpeg
Something's different.
有些不对劲
What was your first clue
你的直觉是啥
that our table is gone
是我们的桌子不见了
or that we woke up missing fingers?
还是我们醒来时失去了手指？
Look. I can finally do this.
看  我终于可以这样了
Don't worry. I can get it out with my other hand.
别担心  我可以用另一只手把它拿出来
I'm good.
我没事
How was Greendale's most colorful study group?
格林戴尔最多彩的学习小组 怎么样了
Wardrobe, not race.
我说服饰  不是肤色
Dean Pelton, you seem extra animated this morning.
佩尔顿院长  您今早看起来格外卡通
That's because it's Spring Cleaning.
那是因为春季大扫除到了
By that i mean the state has cleaned out our spring semester budget
我意思是州政府把我们春季学期的预算都花光了
so we've had to cut corners.
所以我们不得不削减开支
Like our table?
所以我们的桌子没了
Yes, Jeffrey.
是的  杰夫瑞
We're supplementing our income by renting out furniture.
我们通过出租家具来补贴收入
Your table is in...
你们的桌子在...
Kalamazoo for a beer pong tournament.
卡拉马祖  用于啤酒乒乓球锦标赛
In the meantime we've ordered these shorter cheaper tables.
同时  我们订购了这些更小更便宜的桌子
Speaking of budgetary compromises,
说到节约预算
Abed has agreed to be my new dean's assistant comma unpaid.
阿布蒂同意做我的新院长助理 逗号 无薪
You never tweeted that.
你没发过这条推文
Why Abed?
为啥是阿布蒂
Because he was the only one to respond to my email.
因为他是唯一一个回复我邮件的人
Britta@ImpeachBush.Radiohead
布雷塔@弹劾布什.电台头
Abed Nadir, I hereby anoint you Greendale's official Depu-Dean.
阿布蒂·纳迪尔  我在此任命你为格林戴尔正式副院长
Cool cool.
酷 酷
There's a complicated hazing process
本来有个复杂的任命仪式
but we had to slash our pickle budget.
但我们不得不削减杂项开支
Abed, as your first duty,
阿布蒂  作为你的首要职责
We request that you return the study room table.
我们要求归还学习室的桌子
Hold on, Jeffrey.
打住  杰夫瑞
Deaning is not that easy.
院长可不好当
You've got to put the school's interest before your own.
你得把学校的利益放在前面
Oh no!
哦不
I forgot to feed my Tamagotchi.
我忘了喂我的电子宠物了
Daddy's coming.
爸爸来了
Just get our table back.
把我们的桌子拿回来
Sorry Jeff, dean business only.
抱歉 杰夫 只谈公事
Don't worry everyone, I'll get it out with my other hand.
大家别担心  我会用另一只手把它拿出来
Corporate vending machine junk,
资本自动售货机垃圾
give me back my quarters, one percent.
把我的零钱还给我  财阀
Let me help.
让我来帮忙吧
Thanks, Abed.
谢谢  阿布蒂
This is Kyle.
这是凯尔
Yo.
哟
He was sleeping on the lawn.
他刚才睡在草坪上
- I should get back to the dean.  - Wait.
我得回去找院长了   等等
Be careful with that key,
小心那把钥匙
people will try to take advantage of its power.
人们会试图利用它的力量
Like Lord of the Rings.
像指环王一样
That's right, Kyle.
没错  凯尔
Kids on an island.
岛上的孩子们
布姐说的是《蝇王》而非《指环王》
I'm gonna fix him.
我会搞定他的
Hello, Abed.
你好 阿布蒂
In honor of your recent promotion,
为了庆祝你最近的晋升
I wanted to grease the wheels with a Hawthorne bribe basket.
我想用一个霍桑贿赂篮来疏通关系
These babies kept me out of Vietnam.
这些宝贝帮我避开了越战
Sorry, I don't accept bribes.
对不起  我不接受贿赂
I thought you might say that so i also brought this guilt basket.
就知道你会这么说  所以我还带了个愧疚篮
Friendship bracelets, exaggerated medical records,
友谊手镯  夸大的病历
and a picture entitled me and Nelson Mandela
和一张写着「我和曼德拉」的照片
which is an actual photo of you and Danny Glover.
实际上是你和丹尼·格洛弗的合影
丹尼·格洛弗饰演过曼德拉
So about that master key,
对了  那把万能钥匙
I need a favor.
我需要你帮个忙
Fine.
好吧
But I'm not supposed to abuse my power for personal favors,
但我不应该滥用权力谋取私利
so don't tell anyone.
所以不要告诉任何人
（五分钟后）
Pierce told everyone you were handing out favors.
皮尔斯告诉了所有人你在施舍人情
I just need the library left open for a few more hours.
我只需要图书馆多开放几个小时
Every night.
每天晚上
I'd like to use the pool for my son's birthday party.
我想在我儿子的生日聚会上用游泳池
Can you let me into Change's office?
你能让我进昌的办公室吗
He stole my super soaker.
他偷了我的超级水枪
Can you let me into the dean's office?
你能让我进院长办公室吗
He confiscated my super soaker collection.
他没收了我的超级水枪收藏
Abed, what are you doing?
阿布蒂  你在做什么
These favors have got to stop.
别再施舍人情了
But I'm helping my friends.
我是在帮我的朋友
Power is corrupting your judgment.
权力正在腐蚀你的判断力
You have to get rid of that key.
你必须扔掉那把钥匙
This really is like Lord of the Rings.
这真的很指环王
Here you go, Samwise.
给你  山姆卫斯
It's your time now.
现在归你了
Uh, me?
呃  我吗
Everyone else got what they wanted.
其他人都得到了他们想要的
It's only fair that you do too.
你也这么做才公平
Abed, you're very brave.
阿布蒂  你很勇敢
I promise not to abuse this power.
我保证不会滥用这份权力
When did Pierce meet Nelson Mandela?
皮尔斯什么时候见过曼德拉？
Share this food with your brothers.
和你的兄弟们分享这些食物吧
Is this legal?
这合法吗
Morally it'd be illegal to stop.
从道义上讲  不这样才是违法的
Britta?
布雷塔吗
Abed?
阿布蒂
Uh, don't worry. I'm using the key for good.
呃 别担心  我在用钥匙做好事
It's barely stealing.
这不算偷
Busted!
抓到了
Tape recorder justice.
磁带录音机正义
It's barely stealing.
这不算偷
Busted.
抓到了
Tape recorder justice.
磁带录音机正义
Caught by the oldest form of recorder justice.
被早古版的录音机正义抓获
I trusted you, Abed.
我信过你  阿布蒂
It's not his fault.
这不是他的错
I abused Abed's trust to help humanity.
我辜负阿布蒂的信任去人道救助了
This is Kyle.
这是凯尔
Hey.
嘿
You wouldn't know him because he's homeless.
你们不会认识他  因为他是流浪汉
Kyle Schmidt, an online student according to his ID card.
凯尔·施密特  他身份证上写的是在线学生
Student? But...
你是学生？
you sleep in the quad.
但你睡在院子里
Yeah, I like to nap on my lunch break.
是的  我喜欢在午休时间打个盹
I work at the office across the street.
我在街对面的办公室工作
Work? Office?
工作？办公室？
Gah.
啊
I got beard burned from a corporate shill?
老娘的好心被一个资本走狗吃了
This is going on all your records.
这将记录在你们所有人的档案上
Kyle, have you paid your tuition?
凯尔  你交学费了吗
How can I convince you people that I have money.
我怎么才能让你们相信我有钱
Click where it says all students.
点击【所有学生】那里
Wow, look at all these names.
哇  看看这些名字
I wish the state could see this list
我希望州政府能看到这份名单
instead of the one I submitted for fun-  ding.
而不是那份我为了申请资... 趣
Fun-dean. I'm a fun dean.
有趣院长  我是个有趣的院长
Wait a second.
等一下
You haven't been counting online students.
你还没把在线学生算进去
That's our biggest demographic.
这是我们最大的客户群体
Okay, okay. Looks like we've all made mistakes.
好吧  看起来我们都犯过错误
So off you go, I've got an uncomfortable email to write.
你们可以走了  我得写一封令人不爽的邮件
Your tam-a-got-chi has died.
你 的 电 子 宠 物 已 死
Oh, great.
哦  太好了
And now a eulogy?
现在还得写悼词
[Best Dean-Play for "TIME DESK"]
《时光桌》荣获最佳院长剧本奖
S02E09 院长在写他的小说《时光桌》的第一章「邪恶院长传奇」
扮演院长的吉姆·拉什获得过奥斯卡最佳改编剧本奖
So, after plugging in the new numbers,
在导入新增的学生数据后
our state funding has jumped 80 percent,
我们的州拨款猛涨了80%
which was good enough to get your table back.
这足以赎回你们的桌子
I'm sorry. I was so harsh on you, Abed.
对不起  阿布蒂  我对你太苛刻了
It's okay. I don't think I'm depu-dean in material.
没关系  我不觉得我是当副院长的料
It's tough to balance power with friendship.
权衡权力与友谊是很难的
What's happening?
怎么了
You understand me. Oh god.
你居然懂我  哦 天啊
Look at me.
看着我
I'm crying like I've been waiting my whole life to hear that.
我哭得像等了一辈子才听到这句话
Welcome back, table. It's been a long hiatus.
欢迎回来 桌子  真是个漫长的间歇
本片播出时  第三季季中的冬歇期已长达3个月